what is going on everybody today we're
going to switch it up a little bit and
talk about something I have never talked
about on here before obviously majority
of my Channel or my page is solely based
on guns because that's my career but my
office space is full of
sneakers so that's what we're gonna be
doing today today we're gonna be doing a
product review on something that you
guys may have seen if you guys have
liked any sneaker post on Facebook or
Instagram
EB kicks EB kicks has been on my feed
for years years now so today we're going
to be testing out EB kicks's sneaker
care kit we're gonna see what it's all
about and I have three sneakers that I
think are perfect for this job the first
pair that we're going to clean up today
is my 2016 band Jordan Ones now these
aren't really that bad these are just
really really dusty I wear my shoes a
lot now I am a huge huge advocate on
wearing your sneakers do not be afraid
of wearing your sneakers I don't know
about you guys but I work extremely hard
for my money I don't want to spend x
amount of dollars for these sneakers
just to put them in a closet to try not
to scuff them so I am a huge advocate on
wear your sneakers but with coming to
wear your sneakers comes with
sneaker care kit all right and the
second pair we're going to be cleaning
today is my 2018's Jordan 1 unions I've
been to a lot of countries with these
sneakers but there's just times where
I've squatted down I've creased up my
toe box a little bit so now the paint is
kind of hitting up down the toe box
right there so we're gonna yeah so I've
traveled to a lot of countries in these
sneakers and these could just use a good
wash and conditioning and the third pair
of sneakers that we are cleaning today
is something that is very special to my
heart and that is my Travis Scott Jordan
Ones I have traveled everywhere in the
world in these sneakers and when I say
everywhere in the world I mean places
like the Rio Grande I hiked on a
mountain in these damn shoes down to the
Rio Grande to get some hot springs I
have had these in Germany Lithuania
Poland these sneakers were even in
Ukraine this year and I've never cleaned
them like I said I'm a huge advocate of
just wearing your sneakers but I've
never honestly I've never wiped these
down I've never done anything some
people are probably gasping in their
seat but it's okay because I have a
double up pair anyways but that doesn't
give me any justification to not clean
these sneakers so today yeah so today
we're gonna restore these by bringing
these back to life and I'm gonna do that
with the help of Evie kick sneaker care
kit so what comes in the boxes so you
get two bottles of eight fluid ounces of
their shoe cleaner and conditioner you
get one 2.5 ounce of their white touch
up you get the EB kicks brush and sponge
actually there's actually two sponges
here and last but not least you get the
EB kicks microfiber towel so yeah with
all that Ian said let's clean some
sneakers and the first secret we're
going to be cleaning today is the band
one so let's get our products ready
got the brush
the cleaner I also I have the water
right here so so we're gonna wet the
brush
solution
on
work
that's not good
this is so nice
use the EB kicks microfiber towel start
wiping everything away
I'm not going to show you all the result
to the end of the video but wow next
sneaker we're going to be cleaning today
is the Jordan One Union I think I'm
gonna use the sponge on this one because
it does have different kind of materials
that work with the sneaker
the sponge and the water
put the solution on it
and start once you start seeing that
foam
oh yeah
I think what I'm gonna do is I'm
actually gonna take the brush just to
the midsole
guys take this brush
give a little bit of solution
[Music]
let's go ahead and go in on this midsole
wiped off the microfiber
all right and the best for last
the Travis Scott Jordan Ones I'm really
excited to see how these turn out we do
the sponge first and then we'll be doing
the brush with the midsole
all right get the suds in
[Music]
all right let's take the brush now
solution
let's go in on these midsoles
[Music]
all right let me grab our microfiber
all right let's see how we did let's
start off with the band one so this is
how the band One started
Dusty dirty disrespected
and let's see how we ended up
we ended up extremely conditioned very
shiny
crispy clean white
it looks like a brand new sneaker now
the leather just feels so good I want to
say it I think there's coconut oil in
there
the leather just feels extremely
conditioned hence
sneaker cleaner conditioner okay up next
we got the Jordan one unions this is how
we started
the toe box is disgusting
the midsole Tore Up From the Floor Up
and then this is how we ended midsole is
clean
that toe box
night and day
the leather is just super soft I mean
come on now look just look at the
difference of the two toe boxes
[Music]
unreal
and last but not least the sneaker that
I've been looking forward to cleaning
the most the reason why I made this damn
video the Travis Scott Jordan one so
obviously this is how we started this
shoe has never been cleaned since it was
in my possession since 2019.
so we started I've traveled all around
the world I've hiked I've hiked in
Jordan once I don't know anybody else I
can say that height beasts Jordan Ones
so yes this is how we started beat up
Dazed and Confused
and then here's how we ended just really
really nice that toe box man again
look at that look at the diff look at
the difference
just nice clean I do love the patina I
love the yellowing of the midsole it
just gives it that old school Flair Evie
kicks is the truth Man 10 out of 10
recommend if you guys didn't have any
sneakers hype sneakers in general do
yourself a favor do me a favor
get yourself some EV kicks sneaker care
kit I promise you won't regret it hope
you guys enjoyed the video see you guys
in the next one peace
a little bit of bonus footage here you
see my dog actually peed on my son's toy
box so we're gonna try EB kicks for
something a little bit different so I
got the bristle brush here
I'm gonna dip it in the water
see if this works put the solution on
all right grab the microfiber
wow
uh stain's gone come here look what my
shoe cleaner did took away the pee stain
Magic